Joseph Graham

Studying: BSc (Hons) Web Design

Contact

Term address: Leeds Home address: Northallerton

University email: <u>U2154114@unimail.ac.uk</u> Personal email: <u>joseph.adm.graham@gmail.com</u>

Phone: 07305 742522

Portfolio: JosephGraham.co.uk

Personal profile

A highly driven final-year student who always aims to achieve the best results in project work and learn as much as possible. Known for always going the extra mile when it comes to work, putting in extra time to help in team projects. Possesses good experience working and communicating well in many different team environments. Demonstrates a great interest in design and loves working with others to critique and improve each other's work.

Education

BSc (Hons) Web design

University of Huddersfield (2021 - present)

First year modules		Second year modules		Third year modules (Results pending)
Intro to Visual Design	A*	UX Design	A*	Information Architecture
Digital Media Production	A*	Visual Design	A**	Advanced Visual Design
Intro to Web Programming	Α	Video and Post Production	A*	Digital Showcase
Digital Media project 1	Α	Web Development	Α	Final Year Project
Data Analysis	Α	Applied Data Science	Α	
3D and Animation	С	Team Project	Α	

Level 3 Cambridge Technical in IT

Darlington College (2016 - 2021)

Distinction* Distinction* Distinction*

GCSEs

Northallerton School (2016 - 2019)

9 GCSEs including:

Math (5), English Literature (4), English Language (5), ICT (B) and Art (7)

Technical Skills

- Adobe XD, Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, After Effects, Premiere Pro, Animate
- Figma
- HTML
- CSS
- Java Script
- WordPress

Work experience

Kirklees Council (2023 - 2024)

Web Placement Student

- Presented Figma website designs to clients
- Worked in various teams to complete projects
- Maintained and updated multiple Council websites
- Designed and developed web pages
- · Shown adaptability when dealing with large projects with short deadlines
- Communicated professionally with Council members and the public when solving online form issues

Crazy Kingdom soft play (2019 – 2022)

Kitchen assistant/pot-wash

- Worked in a very busy environment as part of a busy team that was always changing
- Experience having to run the kitchen unsupervised using my own initiative
- Dealt with customers politely and efficiently
- Used resourcefulness and critical thinking to solve new unexpected problems.
- Trained new staff

Broomfield School After School Art Club (Jan 2018 - Apr 2018)

Club assistant

- · Taught young children old and new art techniques
- Communicated to various different age groups
- Helped get children active and interested using creativity and resourcefulness
- Organised and displayed children's work

Achievements

Duke of Edinburgh award

- Earned bronze in 2018
- Earned silver in 2019

Award for Academic Excellence in ICT

- Was awarded at the end of GCSEs
- For hard work and dedication to the subject

References

Available on request